20 minutes but they had a whiteboard in the room so i'm just drawing i figured i'll join let y'all
come in figured i'll let y'all watch what i was drawing thank you don't have a mistake kindness
for weakness this ain't no secret y'all see this niggas got me fucked up
oh niggas got me fucked up not today not the one fucked up oh niggas got me fucked up
but i'm not the one just too a masterpiece and dry erase is risky y'all are so funny bro
a masterpiece and dry erase is risky funny as hell what a car is literally driving a car is
literally parked outside driving a car literally just drove by singing killing me softly
you heard it y'all you heard it right thank you kathy that's trippy that's trippy that's trippy
that's trippy that's trippy someone just said topra shank show vibes i did feel an earthquake
of sorts i dreamt i dreamt last night that they took down the apartheid wall
and then right before i went on stage i saw that palestinians in the west bank had taken down or
started to take down the wall i'm still laughing at doing a masterpiece and dry erase is risky
like the way y'all play with language is so funny because risky is such a funny word
risky that's my heppers y'all funny as hell this is my little pre-show mural shout out to my security
because brother amir when we came here today they had taken the whiteboard out and he was like you
want it back you want it back he went and got that whiteboard that's the kind of support i need
you want it back and guess what that shit came back and the drawing was still on it someone said
is there anything you can't do i can't get this phone to sit back i should be going on stage like
literally any second i'm waiting for them to come we're trying to hold the phone for y'all
can y'all see she i actually plan to do that all is india i just don't be having time
i'm trying to do that mama pod i just don't be having time the answer is always i don't be having
time i'm singing your daughter to sleep dickless and what cultures influence my art mostly i would say
aboriginal culture and um congolese and ghanian but it's weird because i was doing this before i
even well aboriginal art i always grew up with because i have a lot of family in australia
but i realized once i started like looking at african art books that i was doing african art
before i had even seen the african art to inspire it so i feel like it's just dna
i'm in it now and tell me i gotta go on stage so if i leave abruptly that's what's happening i'm
supposed to have to perform any minute now i feel like he about to come in here in two minutes
sorry i'm trying to set up the camera oh i'm not a lefty that's just the camera's reversed
i hate to break it to you my month is a lefty though oh my god why is this camera doing this
i'm sorry y'all don't get seasick oh oh we want we want to do american musical standards is that
what we're doing all right y'all i gotta go do a show what no oh i'm eating after if i eat it now
i'll fall asleep i'll be on stage late what we talking about y'all
you